I.
Saw
a. Bomb
.
Bomb. Bomb.
Bomb.
For the.
And. The.
Bring out all of that was so.
You see.
Who's.
Thank.
You. Asto consulted with
which owns about so I don't.
Know. Her know like.
We're all right we're. All right
we're.
All right.
We're. Fine.
All right we're going.
To burn down when. The third day
of March in the year of our large
sixty ninety two. We're the people of
whitewood Massachusetts condemned the.
Nation of claims Clinton Lysol of its
evil. All that's left but blood but made
a break up all the dead and
I think you know I don't.
Already.
Know.
I have made my part but beyond I. Mean.
So short of people white when the battle
is over so when in six hundred ninety two
. What was I said Little is known today
the actual practice of witchcraft the
seventeenth century to England superstition
and jealousy drove the Puritans to
accuse their friends and relatives of
consorting with the. Raiding around huge
bonfire repeating victims chance they can
sign the poor creatures the plates the
tortured souls quite out of the flames
mounted higher and higher burden which
spiral barn. Crazy beat.
That will be all this day. Tomorrow will
be my concluding lecture on the history of
witchcraft in seventeenth
century New England spring
a loss ministrations was
actually. Over the last two.
Months. Since you chose to attend these
lectures I had hoped to put in the spirit
of scientific curiosity. Although.
I think it also done serious
because well hypnotized.
Place about
a date. I look forward for you are. More
of an attraction to my preference rather
than reading through your papers in
a spot only show a very sound
appreciate. To the subject what
a good New England to do my thing your
paper was already quite good you know.
I feel I need some firsthand research I
want to get the atmosphere find out how
widespread witchcraft really was what the
witches were really like it might take
a little time but I have the time my
brother and I were going to spend have
a case with our cousins but
I'd really like to do to get
a room in the smallest oldest town in the
language I can find took through all the
Town Hall Records recheck the libraries
talk to the Puritan center make
a really thorough
investigation. Your brother is
a professor of science but no I hardly
think you'd be very interested in
a history of witchcraft that I go along.
I don't think you'd object to that you
leave Richard to me he's
picking me up here for lunch.
For the blow now and then yeah she's in
there with him. Well I don't like you
getting mixed up in this witchcraft
business right so any bride of
a history course says follow.
Before you go in there could I have
a word with you sure what it's about now
to me. If you're really serious about this
I have been all the town in New England
for this matter of fact identical place
what eventually car did i mention
today's lecture Whitewood. It's quite
a small place is
a little bit up the track so maybe these
directions will help to thank you. I think
you might very well time was looking for
there. I have another woman who only in
the light with a name is new
a space is new it's so just all right such.
Reasons in white flight what's right
word. Now to don't be too
to upset. I'm going to
change my time says a cation
change of plans you know. Going to
a place called White what
for a week or so this is
a message well you know what about Cousin
Sue Well she's expecting you for the
party on the seventeenth you have
a perfectly still you can make
a point and this is important my term
papers got to be good it could mean
a scholarship might
combine to make you have
a good time without me my mind's made up
I'm going to write like that surely any
good encyclopedia will give you all the
nonsense you want to know about which graph
which crap which is not nonsense
I'm sorry risk of witchcraft
black magic sauce to read to me is nothing
but a fairy tale mumbo jumbo from
a scientist Driscoll I believe what I can
see what I can feel and touch the basis
of fairytales is reality the basis
realities fairy tale did you have
a meter which tricycle
perhaps come on your
own
a star and know which ever survive the burning
at the stake for all that back to the
devil. In sixteen hundred ninety two when
the civil servant went to the stake. She
was buried in the churchyard doing that.
And the three years later. Three years
later
a new wave of blood sacrifices broke out
in the village that the dead the daughters
of the elders who were condemned to wear
themselves down there did with every last
drop of blood drained from their bodies
and afterwards people came forward to
testify that they had actually seen less
about selling. This to be more effective
at midnight with
a howling winds and crashing thunder and
even then it wouldn't frighten anyone.
Dick I'm sorry protested.
This or others but.
You will be the first person to discuss the
subject. Tell you when you get to where
it's quite late and I had
swiped one and one sent me
a picture postcard under which. If possible
autographed now I think so much I'm
sorry I have
a date. Now
darling I still don't see why you have to
go up to this white one place. I thought
we were going to have some time together
during this vacation and you know I want
to be with you it's just the look what the
heck can you find that hasn't been found
before. I don't know. It's just that maybe
hidden in some adequate buried in some
old antique shop or
something that might give
a whole new outlook to what new outlook
on the be. A science student how do you
know how important research is but this
isn't about anything real busy just
superstitious people burning silly old
women but suppose the women went silly
suppose they really had
a patent demo. That they could have
supernatural power Oh come on what kind of.
I don't.
It's no use Pharaoh Boatwright our hardest
to talk her out of going. To really
think she will find anything worthwhile
and I think we have to respect
a desire to find something new even if we
if we don't agree with the subject agree
with it I never heard so much nonsense as
that guy Driscoll talks and all my life
oh yeah. As far as not I can say
will stop you from going. Yeah well
I left for this in the car.
I still hope to change your mind don't
worry darling I'm back as quick as I can
right. Don't forget me altogether.
I won't give you my love
and don't forget we have
a dance party. We're done. Excuse
me can you help me I seem to be lost you
are over Jan I'm looking for the one for
grown want for road art anyone uses
it anymore well my friend gave me the
directions I take around twenty eight
a turn on to the one point road that left
in the fork to the White would like to
know I might ask Tom what no man was for
you know many God fearing folks visit
White would now
a days if I were you white if you'll excuse
me I'm going to hurry which way is it
where I'll follow this road about
two miles you Cardwell for to be
a sign won't board road turn left keep
straight there the wife thank you very much
.
That sign saying when Park Road. Lamport
road here good I was afraid I missed it
is it to white would you say yes
I too it would only be imposing
a. Quest to get it aren't you.
Think the highway commissioner does
something about these roads. Push out here
comes another front. What is
your mission in Lightwood
mission. Well I'm going there to do some
research on what's craft. The president
will give us some very interesting lectures
on the subject and I'm going there to
get some original source material. To know
what would happen on it for many years
you go down there they are. Going you must
know the reasons and I should be risking
their own social life.
Mining. I named Jethro P.
Based in each of these to meet you.
Just like
a picture out of the question. He feels I
was in the seventeenth century. Wasn't
what would be. The beaten path you know
Terry it's come here and white or at
times down. Look at that church with
a big beautiful. What
a shame they don't get so. Straight
up yes on the road around.
Ah there it is. Only
a building. Seventeenth century at least.
A picture as can you get right by the
graveyard. Yes it has not been used for
more than two hundred years any which is
buried there. All in
a section of them comes
to. Spook you. Well
keep your fingers crossed Mr King I
hope this is no so I've got room.
Lol.
Oh I didn't hear you come in
are you Mrs new this. Oh.
I was told I might find
a room here. I was recommended by friend
of mine Professor Driscoll that you know
and. Lucky.
I decided to keep you waiting Unfortunately
I cannot talk I have often told her not
to answer the bell. Then your Mrs
No help you yes I'd like to have
a room here for two weeks.
The guests are never
about at this time of the Day Well I'm
a student of us addressed girls he told
me if I mentioned his name I have no
trouble. Well there is
a room I could let you have it's just
off the lobby Thank you. Oh this is no.
Clash is a. Very frontier for being
a witch. She watched and she was
a witch. Come along.
I hope you will be.
The previous occupants of always found it
was agreeable where if there's anything
you should need just ring the bell
for me at the desk thank you.
Oh.
It's been so many months. I've kind of the
days to this holiday so have the others
it was nice the first among my guests to
get here many had to travel that distances
and I was lucky the last few miles were
enchanting because Barlow is very good
company you must be tired general your
room is ready and the festivities.
I am prepared.
Oh this is no less I thought I'd have
a short look around town I won't be gone
long I think you'll find the church
interesting unfortunately
it's no longer has
a congregation. Of. oh Oh.
Please.
I'm told this was once
a house of worship. House of worship on
the river and of this church as long as
the breath of life is within
reach. God. Musta been
a beautiful building. To
do stoop to. I'm sorry.
What
a shame people that phone strangers
rarely come to fight. Well you know I
meant on I'm staying the reason
I have you come talk like. Well
because I'm interested in
witchcraft. I don't know.
Three hundred years the devil has
followed all the. Major G.'s old.
Either has triumphed over here. You. Know
parish. Ships here is. What power
leave like would leave tonight
and they beg you what power to
leave and it is too late.
Good evening. Please excuse the mess we
have been open no. Very interesting things
here yes they belong to my grandmother
and she came back so it turns out. I.
Know my family pretty for
generations but I just came back
a few weeks would you like to have
a look around thank you. Oh I didn't mean
to frighten you when I came in it's just
that all the people I've
met here acted like I'm
a person from another world they don't see
many strangers here and I have the most
. Experience with the reverend he my way
from the church and he talked to me about
curse he warned me to leave whitewash.
Can you explain that. No I can't
Does he often act that way. He's my
grandfather Oh I'm sorry this happened before
you strange is the lack of parishioners
the loss of his side has made him bitter
and suspicious I'm afraid what with him
and the I was very scared when I saw your
lights I made
a dash for them I'm glad you did. Do you
have any books or pamphlets on witchcraft
. A friend of mine well we have
a collection gathering dust but why on
earth would you be interested in the one
size really none of my business no that's
all right I'm studying it in college and
I've come here to write my term paper
so just wait I'll see what I can find.
And if you live with friends of which much
thirty sixty ninety two yes I know I saw
the plaque in the lobby of the hotel you
were staying at the Ravens Yes it was
recommended to me by
a friend of mine Professor Driscoll. Yes
Do you know him now but my grandfather
speaks of him his family come from oh
I didn't know that here I think is
a do for stash. A lovely look at.
The believe it's quite old is a very lucky
I mean more lucky to have found this
a truly worship a New England. Must be
a very rare look. I'm afraid I couldn't
afford to buy it. You can borrow it if you
like could be wonderful I
promise I'll bring it back in
a few days You're very welcome Mr Barlow
Barlow. Thank you very much good night
tonight.
This is not. This is no less
yes Mr. I heard some strange
noises my co-pastor the
water in the pipes this is
a very only and no it seem to be coming
from the cellar underneath hardly think so
must follow the cellars do not extend beneath
your room then wiser trapdoor in. The
ground was filled in many years ago to
strengthen the foundations of the building
but I'm sure if you insist
I will come and see.
I don't hear anything. Just
a few minutes ago. Never mind I'm sorry
you're welcome but you can see for
yourself there is no ring in the trap
door because there is no reason to lifted
there is nothing underneath but.
I don't know.
Do you find this interesting fascinating.
Actually. The first
sixteen hundred ninety two
a coven of which is. Thirteen
some men some women who. Gathered
there. To perform
a black mass in the honor of the
witch. Later to be burned at the stake
marked
a young girl for sacrifice by an
object. With which to call her. And
place a dead bird and
a sprig of Woodbine. The witches
sacrificed the altar and drank her blood
thirty. What thirteen Well
personally I have never had
a clock struck more than twelve.
How about joining the dots in
a while I promise Oh by the way I seem
to have misplaced my locket I remember
having it in my room and disappeared oh
I'm sorry I'm not well I'm not saying it
was stolen it's just I remember having it
on the dresser and now it's gone I would
appreciate it of course I'll
look into it immediately.
I have warned you too often about annoying
I guess if you disobey me again I shall
turn you on and if I turn you out there
will be no place for you anyway you doing
to stand up to do what you.
This follow I'm afraid Lottie is nowhere
to be found but I would I'm glad about
your luggage first thing in the morning
thank you where is everybody most of the
other guests have gone services
services on the first of February.
Candlemas leave. The night when the
witches mock the rituals of the church
are you all right Ms Pearl and. Yes Quite
thank you good night good night was
burning.
If.
FG.
Hi. Larry.
I am Elizabeth so. I'm I'm.
A. Stay as
is. A valid.
List because you call me and you would
have to. Sure if you show up she she
probably met
a good looking he which is bring him along
for the party only the most to lose as
it's not like I want to be late for anything
to worry about she will be here I'm
sure if you make. Us the door I'm
going to recover from dancing that's.
What some of you were expecting somebody
else I guess now and come in come out.
Well now I'm in truth here to
meditate to make here before she left
a white board I should probably go now
that. Number is never late for anything in
our life relax take it easy
join the party she'll be here.
Dick. Dick I haven't had
a letter from now on in over two weeks now
it's probably been too busy working on
a favor. Now there's something wrong I know
it look when you do something for me to
bring up like will you ask I'm
going to shoot left to be serious.
OK.
From long distance I'd like to stick
with. The Ravens and write what.
You know I I don't know the phone number.
Did you give the phone number I know but
that's my sister. They say there's no such
place as the Ravens and. That's
crazy she staying there.
She left in such
a hurry she must've forgotten to return it
to you. That nice Go to me just like she
was going to forget to return
a book you cannot always judge by first
impressions get me. Wrong about people I
know in my books too well perhaps you'll
be more careful in future. Thank you for
letting me have this.
Lucky. Get out of the way you.
Can I hope you were from a sheriff's
office where other callers even
a missing persons report and some college
kid. Part of calling said that the last
known whereabouts of the raid in this part
of the exchange Yes I miss it when did
you last see her two weeks ago she came to
my shopping and I'll just book it quite
valuable I'm not hearing time I decided to
come and get it Mr Newman Saturday night
. A Treatise on devil worship.
I miss but this amid reports.
You think some of these college kids do
nowadays Wow thanks for helping Anjali.
Mary more.
Hello. You know. Please.
You know. OK thank. YOU THANK YOU.
Well. Please send
a card to the Raven then and check
out two weeks ago. And get it when
I I do. That is
a man's books and papers going through them
so if you can find anything which might
give us a lead I'm going to pay a visit to
a colleague of mine. Who
knows of like accept the sacrifice.
I follow and I commend. Course please do
thank you cause I don't owe you last night
but I guess you want it knowing
what. You're going to study.
That is all done thanks. You take
a drink ran sort of. Ways. What's on your
mind tonight is missing and she has been
since the day after she arrived right what
made you quite sure. So the police said
What are they doing about it. Carrying out
a routine check I don't suppose I can do
much more until I got something definite
to go on but there was a very great
deal more they could do what if I was
a concern she disappeared two weeks ago
and one of the but I think the know
anything about it when you come see me
for I thought you might have some ideas
right it is that I whiteboard because it
was the best place for research and you
suggest that you say the Ravens then sure
it's the only in the race but not from
number then has it's OK on tell Bob No
it doesn't need to Avatar you know it so
well because I was born and worked with
I see you would have every reason to
believe she'd be perfectly safe in going
there no reason to suppose that she
wouldn't be. Struck me as being perfectly
capable of taking care of herself Granger
back but why did she come back and I don't
know about all I can understand your
anxiety but I'm quite sure there's nothing
to worry about nothing at all she's
probably got absorbed the subject is going
off someplace I wish that my class had
her application and I'm going to find out
whether the application letter I'm going
to retrace every step now and talk I'm
either going to find now don't know what
happened.
I can't stop you. For
a. While but I think your sister somebody
else went along trying to find out about
it same thing might happen to them possible
you seem to think something happened to
my sister that you know I just think you're
jumping to conclusions maybe I can find
. Yes. Of course
please come in black and white
what. Do you think he's going to
likely. Be Surprised I
just can't prove my point.
Quite
a coincidence my own family I'm going to
work with matter of fact I was born there
yes I know please thank you
for. Their progress no thank
you. I think you know my grandfather
the Reverend Russell Russell
Well yes of course I do I want to be living
in what would send my grandmother died
a few weeks ago oh I'm sorry. On
I'll go help you I've come about
a pupil of yours but I know now and God Oh
yes she came to plywood two weeks ago I
made tonight when she told me that she was
a student in one of your classes that you
recommended that she stay at the Ravens
and is quite right it does well that's
what I've come to see you about on the day
after she arrived she disappeared.
Later the police came asking questions
a family were worried I thought you might
have their address and why do you want
a family's address because I have something
of hers I want to return and well you
just leave it with me and make sure they
get it safely. I don't want to trouble you
if if you just give me their ID
to his. As you wish. Her address
is door just to street two to five she
lives with her brother matter of fact he's
a colleague of mine you just met leaving
when you arrived. Now if you'll excuse me
I've got
a lot of work to do one rather busy man of
my own cause thank you for your help now
though I hope to see something.
You were about the wanted to buy
that was rusty.
Old. Man's luggage
a right. As I know it to me I gave it to
where did you get it the servant at the
end gave it to me strange I don't think she
want to miss and you was to know I had
it known that she runs the. Why did you
come to him with this rifle I found this.
Professor This was not a paper
I found in the pages of
a book I lent your sister on her first
evening and why Ford and she didn't return
it I went to the hotel What was the book
an old book book about witchcraft do you
believe in it Miss Russell I don't know
sometimes I almost think I live with live
with that section of my grandfather's up
to now I didn't take him very seriously
he's an old man. Now I'm beginning to
wonder what he says isn't true what does he
say there's something evil about the
village on certain nights the inhabitants
leave the streets close their doors and
stay behind them. And on these nights the
dead come to life. I'd like Councilman
save. You know about candle Missy's.
Which in one of nine books.
I don't believe in things like this don't
happen today. I swear I wonder if I'm
going to white with tomorrow after classes
that I can give you honest Thank you but
I must get back I can't leave my grandfather
alone he's blind come and see you when
I arrive I just like to have
a talk with him please do it the house
make the church back. I'll see to that or.
Would you be going to White would. Yes
Would you take me along with you the dock
night for walking.
Tom. The Reverend Russell
granddaughter which is
this how did you I know
a great deal about what would you have
been the number. Of Missing you give me
is a special privilege to visit for
a job if you. Sat me. Will soon be
a delight with.
Far as I go you will.
See is pretty to the issue
that I have to take
a living the symbols of those workers.
Somehow seems to make it better.
Another day. And tomorrow.
What's right around what road straight
ahead fork in the road you see
a sign turn left you heading for white
would I am many people have this way not
many That's the only way and I'm out
of the town list wrenching yet it was
a member by any chance a pretty
girl in a convertible about
a month ago gone I'll go read about her
the papers never seen her again told the
police.
The in the.
Corner Could you tell me the way to White
would please the ones straight ahead fork
in the road see
a sign won't board road turn left it's
your right Ian but thanks everyone young
fella they don't like strangers and
white OK fine thanks very much to.
Pull some of those.
Old.
Good evening good evening I'd like to run
plays the end is closing. And only be
here
a few days but the Internet is closing one
in today but if you don't mind I'd like
standalone. If you insist. You can i
can i have
a year the same room my my sister hand
still available as and yes it's available
with
a lot of you told the police and my sister
checked out you are mistaken Mr Barlow I
told them that on the morning of February
second I went to Iran and found it empty
had not slept in her luggage and car
gone and had Bill and paid remember the
charges on mine when was the last time you
saw on the evening of February first it
was shortly before midnight she'd been in
the lobby here dancing with some of the
guests she seemed to be enjoying herself
did any particular guest play or
a special attention to them not that I
noticed your sister kept very much to
yourself you know why she came to white
board it is not my habit to inquire into
people's private business were the fact
that she was she was investigating
witchcraft and antagonized anyone in the
village. Hardly they have been other
students here you know
beside your sister was
a very agreeable and likeable young woman
have you any idea where she might have
gone. Now thank you and I
see the room as you wish it
is this way.
If you should need anything and I am not
of the day you have only to ring the bell
again.
Hello I'm so glad you've come. I saw your
car outside readings in earlier I want to
put it happen to you every Talking with
this is nervous in the night I took
a walk around the village find out anything.
Everyone here seems to be afraid of
something you don't think is just my
imagination I don't know who's to say we're
imagination and the truth begins this is
nothing tangible it's. This is where they
look at you I sold it to. Me I
see the book at Mandarin Yes I
put
a marker between the pages which you must
stop treating just sit down and I'll tell
my grandfather you're here thank you.
This is.
I warned you.
Grandfather this is mystified how do you
do since God be with you so we sit where
will be more comfortable. Your
children for this must be
time. He does I have
a little six missed these days for the
fight. Won't you sit down and make some
coffee to fight against what Mr Russell
against even though the decision this
village. People are creatures of the devil
they know no other god you mean they
were so Satan today Satanism was never
stronger than at the present time two
hundred years the people of light would
have carried out all rituals the church is
teaching I find it very hard to believe
I do not doubt my son it is real enough
for years I struggled against that which
is the master to go in my sight incredible
. To convince others. To
follow that unbelievable.
People have
a pact with the devil to worship
him and do his work in return he
gives them eternal life to write.
Under seal the sparkle they must
sacrifice
a young girl on two nights of the
year when other nights can see. Which
is. February the first
one is which is Sabbath
tonight now you know why I came
to see. The idea it was so
late May I I have a rain check
on the coffee I like to have
a few words in the snow this again.
I was wrong to think that man's disappearance
is connected in some way with the
witches ceremonies. When I
would like to come back later.
And my name is Pat mine's written I think
I feel better now you are here and I'm
going to spend it I found out what
happened there Nann. Take care.
Adding to cause
a different color. Must not see that
young man again tonight I know the devil
comes in Miletus guy says. I get your.
Father disappeared. Tomorrow you go into
a good the front door. Shut
the door on your way. Out
of what is it me listen I
does it this is their side the richest
side. Can we do we must leave here
leave here immediately.
By the cars.
Coming from. The
pump I know.
There was. A lie when Reagan.
Mr Barlow for me yes. I don't see
it becoming taboo danger we've got the
fight we want to enjoy it from what we've
got the. Fact that we shot. Fired.
IT'S IT'S IT'S IT'S IT'S.
Let's have another Russell so
which you know he has which.
Destroys it throughout the
house shadow of the cross. To
cross. Creek you.
The Living God.
For when the baby
was too much what happened.
Why.
Why. Why.
Or why. You're.
One. Of the but.
The.
Oh God greatest.
Tommy didn't read. A book and.
They all. Know. That I am
a rough.
The.
Backlash. Started. Yet I
was.
Going to.
Take it to be.
Addressed.
It comes nearest.
With.
The.
Same. Gun is it with the newest.
Saw
a. Few
feet. A few.
Feet.
ah
Ah
.